thinklandingpages.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy | Think Landing Pages

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your private information is our priority.  This Statement of Privacy applies to thinklandingpages.com and Think Industries, LLC and governs data collection and usage.  For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Think Industries, LLC include thinklandingpages.com and vice versa.  By using thinklandingpages.com, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Think Industries, LLC may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name and email address.  If you purchase Think Industries, LLC products or services, we collect billing and credit card information.  This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.  We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected.  This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses.  This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of Think Industries, LLC websites.

Think Industries, LLC encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Think Industries, LLC websites so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Think Industries, LLC collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services and products requested.

Think Industries, LLC may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Think Industries, LLC.  Think Industries, LLC may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services and products or of potential new services and products that may be offered.

Think Industries, LLC does not sell, rent or lease its customer list to third parties.

Think Industries, LLC may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, arrange deliveries, or aid Think Industries, LLC in completing other functions necessary for business.  All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Think Industries, LLC, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Think Industries, LLC may keep track of the pages users visit within our websites.  This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising.

Think Industries, LLC will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Think Industries, LLC or its websites; (b) protect and defend the rights of Think Industries, LLC; and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

Think Industries, LLC may use cookies on its websites.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)
